

Maxim Sheshukov

15/11/1988 ● Russian ● Moscow, Russia ● sheshukov.maxim@gmail.com

• github/skype: go-maxus-go

Results-focused software developer with 5+ years experience designing and implementing cross-platform user interface applications. Well-versed in producing efficient, easy-readable, scalable, reusable and covered by tests code. Initiative and creative, constantly looking for ways to improve a product and development process.

Education

Physics, master degree 09/2006 - 06/2012

Novosibirsk State University, Russia

Department of automation physical and technical researches

Work experience

Senior C++ Developer 11/2018 - present Luxoft, Escape Technologies, Moscow

- Speeded up database by 30% by implementing a LRU cache system
- Decreased legacy bugs population by development a crossplatform unit test system

Middle C++ Developer 03/2016 - 12/2017

Movavi, 2Gis, Novosibirsk

- Implemented a slideshow master which became a successful separate product
- Increased video editor's selling by 10% by maintaining tutorials

Junior C++ Developer 11/2013 - 03/2016 SoftLab-NSK, Novoribirsk

• Developed safe bulletless biathlon training system for children

Additional experience

Teacher at the university

01/2016 - 06/2016

Novosibirsk State University, Novosibirsk

 Taught object oriented programming course for a second year group of fifteen students at the University

Self-employed developer 06/2018 - 11/2018

Work from home, Moscow

- Gained experience of producing and publication of own application <u>Foody</u>
- Opened the mind by looking into Android operating system

Skills

Coding **Development** Languages Russian C++ Git Native STL OOP English Advanced Algorithms Qt **Boost TDD**

Hobbies











Programming

App Development

Computer Games

Traveling

Reading

Strengths

Quick learning C